<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string name="help_content"><![CDATA[

<!DOCTYPE HTML>
<html><head>
<meta http-equiv="Content-Type" content="text/html; charset=utf-8">
<title>CallRecording</title>

<style>
body{
text-align: justify;
font-family: Tahoma;
}
</style>
</head>

<body>
<h2>Call Recording</h2>
<ol>
<li><a href="#about">About the program</a></li>
<li><a href="#first">First calls</a></li>
<li><a href="#interface">Program interface</a></li>
<li><a href="#call_mark">How to add a note during
conversation</a></li>
<li><a href="#audio_source">Can\'t hear the person
speaking in the recording. What to do?</a></li>
<li><a href="#hidden">Invisible mode</a></li>
</ol>
<a name="about"></a>
<h3>Program Info</h3>
This is a program for recording conversation and adding
notes to the recorded conversations. <br>
After you end the call, the program will ask if you would like to save
the recording of the conversation onto the memory card. The program
helps you to keep records of important conversations and to find them
in the history of conversations, thanks to the text and visual notes.
Having Call Recording makes working with a large number of clients a
breeze.<br>
<a name="first"></a>
<h3>First calls</h3>
Immediately after installation of the program the list of recorded
conversations is empty. What a surprise! :) At this moment you do not
have any recorded conversations and in order to test the program you
need to make a phone call to any number as you normally would. After
that, launch Call Recording and you will see your conversation in
the list of recorded calls. Now you can hear it by pressing the "Play"
button.<br>
<a name="interface"></a>
<h3>Program interface</h3>
The Program Interface consists of several pages.<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;">CALLS</span>
-
contains the history of all saved conversations, grouped by days.<br>
</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;">NOTES</span>
-
contains a similar list but only shows recorded conversations that have
a note attached to them.<br>
</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;">DIALOGUES</span>
-
contains a similar list of all recorded conversations, but this list is
grouped by client.<br>
</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;">PLANNED</span>
-
contains calls that you have planned to make in the future. Here the
sorting order is reversed, the earliest planned call will be at the top
of the list.</p>
<a name="call_mark"></a>
<h3>How to write a note during conversation</h3>
<p>Often, when we are talking with someone, it is necessary to
record some information that he/she dictates. This could be a phone
number, address or other important piece of information.
</p>
<p>In order to add a note to an ongoing conversation all you have
to do is
pull down the notification panel at the top of the screen, and select
the icon for Call Recording, and you will get a screen where you can
add a note to the conversation. Therefore, you are able to speak with a
person and type keywords and information, which you will than see in
the list of conversations, next to the phone number of the client.</p>
<a name="audio_source"></a>
<h3>I can\'t hear the other person talking in the recorded
conversation. What to do?</h3>
All conversations recorded by the program are responsibility of
the&nbsp;<span style="font-weight: bold;">Audio Source</span>.
If you go into configuration and choose <span style="font-weight: bold;">Audio Source</span> you
will see the following 5 options:<br>
<ol>
<li>Default</li>
<li>Microphone</li>
<li>Voice Uplink</li>
<li>Voice Downlink</li>
<li>Voice Call (input and output streams)</li>
</ol>
The names of these Sources are deceptive and could cause confusion,
because every current manufacturer of mobile phones interprets them as
it is convenient for them. On certain models of phones microphone
recording captures both streams, but on others both streams are
captured when the<span style="font-weight: bold;"> Output
Stream</span> option is selected. All that we can do is
experiment in order to achieve the correct recording configuration. We
hope that in the near future, manufacturers of devices will more
strictly adhere to specifications from Android and the names of sound
sources will correspond to how the device will actually record.
<p>The first option, <span style="font-weight: bold;">Default</span>,
is supported by every device, and thereby we
set it as the default after installation. When using this option some
devices record both streams, but some record only your voice. Try
selecting a different Recording Source and to re-record the
conversation. Also it is important to note that some telephone models
do not support recording of two-way streams without Root-Permissions.</p>
<a name="hidden"></a>
<h3>Invisible mode</h3>
<p>Call Recording can be configured to work in the Invisible
mode. For this all you do is remove the checkmark of the&nbsp;<span style="font-weight: bold;">Icon in
status panel</span> and set configuration named <span style="font-weight: bold;">Conversation recording</span>
to&nbsp;<span style="font-weight: bold;">Record all</span>.
</p>
<p>This way the program will not ask you "Would you like to save
this
conversation?" at the end of a phone call, and the application icon at
the top of the screen will not be visible. Now your Call Recording
is working in the invisible mode.
</p>
<p></p>
</body></html>

]]>
    </string>
</resources>